take40.com 2016-07-12

# Take 40 | Top 40 Countdown Australia | Music Charts

### Version 3.0 - Last updated 25 August 2014

Authentic Entertainment Pty Ltd of Level 4, 21-31 Goodwood Street, Richmond, Victoria 3121, Australia (Authentic) is bound by the Australian Privacy Principles set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the Act) and is committed to protecting the privacy of any personal information you provide to us.

Authentic will only collect, use or disclose personal information in accordance with the Act and this Privacy Policy.

Authentic may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. The updated version will be available by following the "Privacy Policy" link on any of our websites, including www.take40.com and www.thehothits.com. 

In this Privacy Policy, "personal information" has the meaning set out in the Act. Basically, personal information means information or an opinion about an individual who is reasonably identifiable. 

### 1\. Collection of Personal Information

The collection of personal information depends on how you deal with Authentic. The most common ways we collect personal information are described below.

To access certain features of Authentic websites, you may need to register as a member. Authentic requires that you provide certain personal information (such as your name, email address, postcode, password, age, gender and mobile phone number) in order to register as a user of those features.

To enter a promotion or competition, you will need to provide certain personal information (such as your name and contact details).

If you contact us with a question or comment, we may collect certain personal information for the purposes of responding to your question or comment. 

We may also collect personal information about you from publicly available sources, from our related companies or from third parties.

### 2\. Use of personal information

The purposes for which we use your personal information will depend on the circumstances in which we collected it. The most common ways we use personal information are described below.

Generally, we may use your personal information:

  * for the purposes for which we collected it (and related purposes which would be reasonably expected by you);
  * for other purposes to which you have consented; and
  * as otherwise authorised or required by law.

When you use or register as a user of any of our websites, Authentic may use the information we collect:

  * to monitor who is accessing the website or using services offered on the website;
  * to profile the type of people accessing the website;
  * to tailor the information on the website to your personal preferences; and
  * unless you opt-out of receiving communications, to send you information about our services and products and services and products of our third party suppliers and 'partners' (such as record companies) by email or SMS.

When you enter a promotion or competition, Authentic may use the information we collect:

  * to administer the competition or promotion; 
  * to award or administer prizes; and 
  * unless you opt-out of receiving communications, to send you information about our services and products and services and products of our third party suppliers and 'partners' (such as record companies) by email or SMS.

If you contact us with a question or comment, we may use your personal information to respond to your question or comment. 

### 3\. Disclosure of personal information

Authentic may disclose your personal information to third parties in connection with the purposes described in section 2 of this Privacy Policy.

Generally, we will only disclose your personal information to a third party if:

  * that disclosure is required for the purposes for which we collected the information;
  * you have consented to that disclosure;
  * we are required by law to disclose the information; or
  * we are otherwise permitted to disclose the information under the Australian Privacy Principles.

The third parties to which we may disclose your personal information include:

  * related companies;
  * contractors (such as mailing houses, marketing agencies, website and data hosting providers and other IT suppliers) and others persons who perform services for us;
  * companies who may use your personal information in order to tailor electronic advertising to you (e.g. on a webpage) in relation to our products and services;
  * our accountants, insurers, lawyers, auditors and other professional advisers;
  * in the unlikely event that we or our assets may be acquired or considered for acquisition by a third party, that third party and its advisors; and
  * third parties that require the information for law enforcement or to prevent a serious threat to public safety.

We do not generally disclose personal information to overseas entities, although it is possible that some of the above entities may be located overseas.

Where we disclose your personal information to third parties (whether in Australia or overseas), we will use reasonable commercial efforts to ensure that such third parties protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Some information that you post to parts of our websites or to social media pages may be available to be viewed by the public. You should use discretion is deciding what information you upload to such sites.

### 4\. Security of Personal Information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that personal information that Authentic collects from you is kept secure through the facilities provided by our secure corporate database. While we exercise great care in relation to the security of your personal information, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Authentic does not ensure or warrant the security of any personal information transmitted to or from our websites and you use our websites at your own risk.

### 5\. How to seek access to or correction of your Personal Information

You may seek access to personal information which Authentic holds about you by contacting us as described in section 8 of this Privacy Policy. We will provide access to that information in accordance with the Act, subject to certain exemptions which may apply. We may require that the person requesting access provide suitable identification and where permitted by law we may charge an administration fee for granting access to information.

If you become aware that any personal information we hold about you is incorrect or if you wish to update your information, please contact Authentic as described in section 8 of this Privacy Policy.

### 6\. Cookies and third-party advertising on Authentic websites

Cookies are small text files stored on your computer to enable a web server to collect information from your web browser. Cookies store information such as the web pages you have visited and how you have used a website. They do not automatically collect personal information about you, although if you provide personal information through our websites, then that information may be stored in a cookie.

Authentic uses cookies to help us monitor how you use our websites and the internet so that we can customise and improve the website content. Authentic may also use cookies to personalise your experience at the website and to save your login details. Authentic does not disclose information gathered from cookies to third parties, other than to its website developers. 

Authentic also uses Google Analytics, a cookie-based service provided by Google. Authentic uses a feature of Google Analytics referred to as Demographics and Interest Reporting, which collects data relating to the demographics (age and gender) and interests of visitors to our websites for the purpose of analysing how visitors engage with our websites. This data is stored on Google's servers and is accessible by Google in accordance with Google's Privacy Policy.

Some of the third-party advertisers who advertise on Authenticâs websites may also place their own cookies on your computer to monitor the effectiveness of their advertising. This enables them to understand where you saw their advertisement and to target their online advertisements more effectively. These cookies collect information about the web pages you have visited. They do not collect any personal information about you or your computer. The information gathered from these cookies is collected directly by the third-party advertiser (or their agency) and is not accessed by Authentic.

You can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from enjoying the full functionality of the Website. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information.

You can opt out of Google Analytics by visiting www.youronlinechoices.com.au or Googleâs opt-out site at tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

You can opt-out of certain third-party advertiser cookies by visiting www.youronlinechoices.com.au or by visiting the advertiserâs website.

### 7\. Links to third party websites

Authentic provides links to and from third party websites that are not operated or controlled by Authentic and may not be subject to a privacy policy. Authentic is not responsible for the conduct of these third parties. Before disclosing personal information to any third party we suggest you examine the privacy policies on the third party's website or enquire about their privacy policy.

### 8\. Complaints, queries, further information

We welcome your queries or comments about our Privacy Policy and personal information handling practices. 

If you would like further information on our personal information handling practices or wish to make a complaint about a breach by Authentic of the Australian Privacy Principles or this Privacy Policy, please contact the Authentic Privacy Officer at privacy@mcmentertainment.com or Authentic Entertainment Pty Ltd, Level 4, 21-31 Goodwood Street, Richmond, Victoria, 3121.

We take all complaints seriously and will assess and investigate any complaint received with the aim of resolving it in a timely and efficient manner. 

If you are not satisfied with the outcome of a complaint or are interested in obtaining additional information on privacy issues, you may wish to contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner through its website at www.oaic.gov.au.
